Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Richard V. Szary, head of Manuscripts and Archives, records, 1975-2002; Accession 2013-A-027
  - Yale-China Association-file transfer, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Architecture and Engineering Services-file transfer, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Beinecke freezer, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Microfilm project-History of Women at Yale, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - EAD/XML, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Dissertations, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Archives 300, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Archives 300 planning, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Archives 300 Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Archives 300-budget reports to the university, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - University Archives manual, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 101-102)
  - Exhibit photographs-Sterling Memorial Library renovations correspondence, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Collections correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - University Archives-records services, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - University Archives-access policies of other institutions, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - University Archives-access policies for student records in MS groups, 1990, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - University Archives-press clipping on class records, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - University Archives-Yale publications, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - University Archives long-term planning, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - University Archives finding aid project, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - 149 York Street flood, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Storage-149 York Street, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Storage vaults, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Mary LaFogg, head of Collections Management, records, 1972-2008; Accession 2013-A-029
  Restricted until January 1, 2043.
  - Administration and Support
    - Administrative Assistant/Associate (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Audit Report-Manuscripts and Archives 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Budget (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Equipment-automation (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Equipment-lockers (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Equipment/Furnishings-information/ergonomics (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Equipment/Furnishings-non-automation-requests (Box 1, Folder 7-11)
    - Equipment/Furnishings-public services (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Facilities database-repairs/maintenance (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Facilities-alterations (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Human Resources: Orientation/new staff and departing staff checklists (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Human Resources: Student employment (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Licensing procedures and fees (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Manuscripts and Archives Procedures
      - Emergency procedures (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Essential services (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Evacuation procedures (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Inclement weather policy (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Information (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Mission statements (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Portraits in the department (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Systems
        - Automated registration (Box 1, Folder 26)
        - CMS 3.0 (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - Departmental intranet (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - Digital resources priorities and activities (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - Location database (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - Office of origin (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - Orbis uploads (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - Planning documents (Box 1, Folder 33)
        - Use database (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Numismatics collection (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Staff safety (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Arrangement and Description
    - Accession management (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Backlog management (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Coins, stamps, and paper ephemera (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Describing Archives: A Content Standard (DACS) (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Digital library rescue repository (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Digitizing duplicating masters (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Dissertations (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - ES/Yale EAD conversion project 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 44-45)
    - Frank Gehry architectural archives (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Labeling processed collections (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Legal collections processing project (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Minimum standards (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Processing and storage costs (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - SAA EAD outsourcing session 2004 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Yale oral history project (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Collection Development
    Restricted until January 1, 2083.
    - Aluka Reddy Project, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Artemis Project, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Collection Development retreat, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Donars
      - Cadwalader, Wickersham & Taft, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Faculty papers, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Manuscripts and Archives collection policy, 1980-1983, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Manuscripts and Archives future microform projects, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Publications Working Group, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Selector Information, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Collections Management
    - Archivists Toolkit (AT) (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Brittle materials service point (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Collections valuation-Manuscripts and Archives Risk Assessment Report 1993 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Collections management-definitions/retreat discussions (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Collection management systems (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Data loggers (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Library Shelving Facility (LSF)
      - Arts Library transfers (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - Batch job issues (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - Budget requests (Box 2, Folder 74-79)
      - Checklist for direct transfers and pallet instructions (Box 2, Folder 80)
      - General information (Box 2, Folder 81)
      - Operational considerations (Box 2, Folder 82)
      - Oversize materials (Box 2, Folder 83)
      - Processing workflow (Box 2, Folder 84)
      - Site construction expansion planning (Box 2, Folder 85)
      - Special Collections materials (Box 2, Folder 86)
      - Split collections (Box 2, Folder 87)
      - Statistics (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - LSFR issues (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - L and B egress job meeetings and correspondence 2008 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Not-on-shelf (NOS) procedures (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Orbis2
      - Circulation (Box 2, Folder 92)
      - Item record creation programs (Box 2, Folder 93)
      - Location mapping item types (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Paradox replacement meeting (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Pilsudski film production (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Preservation (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Preservation Technologies, PA (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Risk management fine arts materials-February 2003 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Scrapbooks project (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Security
      Restricted to Office of Origin only.
      - Audits, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 101)
      - Beinecke Rare Bok Library, 2001, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 102)
      - File project, 1994-1995, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 103)
      - Information, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 104)
      - Keys, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 105)
      - Key control and card swipe access systems, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 106)
      - Manuscripts and Archives overall, 1988-2002 (Box 2, Folder 107)
      - Manuscripts and Archives system, 1992-1994, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 108)
      - Manuscripts and Archives Working Group, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 109)
      - Objects policy, 1992, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 110)
      - Patron information, 1984-1995 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Serials project (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Video Archive of Holocaust Testimonies (VAHT)
      - Item record creation, LSF prep, LSF reconciliation (Box 2, Folder 113)
      - Robotic preservation/digitization project (SAMMA) (Box 2, Folder 114)
      - Video tape restoration (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Wireless upgrade 2008 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Collection Shelving and Space
    - Space
      - B57, B57-A, B57-B cleaning/dust issues (Box 2, Folder 117)
      - B69 compact shelving (Box 2, Folder 118)
      - B69-B71A (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Library-Coordination and Information
    - BRBL building future committee (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - BRBL fortieth anniversary (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Comittee on Action Planning (CAP) (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Digital Production and Integration Prorgram (DPIP) (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Eli Express process improvement/special collections (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Integrated Library Technology Services (ILTS)-formerly Library Systems Office (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - JDC PTO (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Library collection security report implementation (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Library collection space management program (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Library director (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Library financial plan (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Library financial aid steering committee (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Library human resources (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Library integrated access program (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Library Joint Departmental Committee (JDC) (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Library learning plan (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Library Microcosm Group (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Library mission, goals, and objectives (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Library organizational models, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Library planning process 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Library priorities, Report on the Staff Survey (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Library space planning memoranda and reports (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Library Space Planning Task Force (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Library working model, 1986-1996 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - LMC Task Force on Library Business Practices (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - LMC Photocopy Task Force (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Performance Expectations Task Force 1986 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Sterling Memorial Library 75th anniversary (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Strike contigency plan (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Yale University Library finding aid program (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Yale University Library tax exempt number (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Yale University Library withdrawal policy 1993 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Professional Activity
    - BRBL/LSF (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Chinese archivists program (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Library Collection Security Group (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Library Collection Security Group-staff guidelines (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Library Security/Risk Management Team (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Public Programs and Research Services
    - EAD Finding Aid Group (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Exhibits and procedures (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Film sales and film list on web (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Manuscripts and Archives-microforms readers policy (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Manuscripts and Archives-public workstations (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Manuscripts and Archives-publications available (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Office of origin (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Patron registration (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Publications-HLS (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Publications-Yale Daily News (YDN) (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Reference consultations (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Reference minimum standards (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Reference renovation-Cowles Reference Center (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Reprographics and imaging services manual (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Scholarly Resources Inc-microfoms distribution (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - SML supervised reading room (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Video/audio production guidelines and fees (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Yale University
    - Administration (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Architectural archives project (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Employee assistance program (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Facilities (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Human Resources-C and T position classification review (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Human Resources-M and P position classification review (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Office of the President (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Yale Archives
      - Architectural archives program (Box 3, Folder 181)
      - Audio visual database (Box 3, Folder 182)
      - Dissertations (Box 3, Folder 183)
      - Guide to services (Box 3, Folder 184)
      - Information (Box 3, Folder 185)
      - Picture collection (Box 3, Folder 186)
      - Publications (Box 3, Folder 188)
      - RU conversion (Box 3, Folder 189)
      - Tercentennial (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Planning and Miscellaneous Files
    - Planning Reports
      - 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 191)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 192)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 193)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 194)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 195)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 196)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 197)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 198)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 199)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 200)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 201)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 202)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 203)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Manuscripts and Archives-strategic planning (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Manuscripts and Archives-strategic planning readings (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Electronic Scriptorum (ES) (Box 4, Folder 219)
      - Yale finding aids specifications (Box 4, Folder 207)
      - Finding aids quality control (Box 4, Folder 208)
      - EAD-MARC 856 field linking (Box 4, Folder 209)
      - EAD retreat documents (Box 4, Folder 210)
      - RLG best practice guidelines for EAD (Box 4, Folder 211)
      - Yale project (Box 4, Folder 212)
      - Meetings and reports (Box 4, Folder 213)
      - Budget and recommendations (Box 4, Folder 214)
      - Contract and invoices (Box 4, Folder 215)
      - Finding aid page counts (Box 4, Folder 216)
      - Finding aids production manual (Box 4, Folder 217)
      - EAD project notebook (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Space Planning
      - Room B-50 fit-out project manual specifications (Box 4, Folder 219)
      - Room B-57 punch list (Box 4, Folder 220)
      - Project schedule and budget (Box 4, Folder 221)
      - Program notes (Box 4, Folder 222)
      - E-mail (Box 4, Folder 223)
      - Minutes (Box 4, Folder 224)
      - Plans (Box 4, Folder 225)
      - Room B-57 voice/data (Box 4, Folder 226)
      - B/C vault project information (Box 4, Folder 227)
      - Meetings 2003 (Box 4, Folder 228)
  - Annual Reports
    - 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 251)
- Records, 1952-2007; Accession 2013-A-031
  The accession consists of correspondence with dealers, transfers, and closed and deactivated files.
  - Correspondence with Dealers
    - Dealers, correspondence with (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Dealers, rejected (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Transfers
    - General, 1952-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4-34)
      No file for 1985.
    - Ilardi microfilm collection (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - World War I posters (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Theater programs (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Survey of business records prior to transfer to various institutions (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Art and Architecture Library (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Audio Visual/Film Study Center (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Babylonian Collection (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library (Box 1, Folder 46-49)
    - Bibliography Department (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Divinity Library (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Drama Library-School of Drama (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Epidemiology and Public Health Library (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Forestry Library (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Franklin collection (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Historical Sound Recordings (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Judaica collection (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Lewis Walpole Library (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Medical Historical Library (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Microform Room (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Music Library (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Numismatic collection (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Peabody Museum (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Preservation Department (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Slavic collection (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Yale Art Gallery (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Yale Center for British Art (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Yale Law Library (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Yale Medical Library (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Yale University Library-general (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Closed or Deactivated Proposals
    - Civil Rights Project (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Father Divine (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Hindermith collection (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Wilson Family papers (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Financial records of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, 2011-2012; Accession 2014-A-007
  Restricted until January 1, 2047
  The dates of the records for accession 2014-A-007 are for the fiscal year 2011-2012 unless otherwise specified.
  - Account files
    - Class of 1884 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Kahn (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Kissinger-CF (Conference) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Kissinger-current use (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Yale memorabilia (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Library special collections-archives (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Library special collections-departmental (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Architecture-Levis (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Library books-gifts (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Lindbergh photo project (block) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - P-card (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Whitney Family papers (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Archive services (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Learning plan (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Public Services
      - Weekly deposits (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Invoices (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Credit card (American Express) (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Credit card (Visa/Master Card) (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Royalties (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Professional travel (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Payroll
      - Student wages (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Temps and casuals (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Monthly Account Summaries
    - Book 1: Bingham Archives, Bingham Departmental, Class of 1884, Driggs, Kahn, Library Collections-Archives, Library Collections-Departmental, Kissinger Papers Archivist, Kissinger CF (Conference), Kissinger Current Use, Lindbergh, Seymour, Yale Memorabilia, Archives Space/Building a Next Gen (Box 2, Folder 23-25)
    - Book 2: Architecture-Dudley, Architecture-Levis, Architecture-Nelson, Artemis-Students, Buckley Papers, Discretionary Law Library, GLBTQ, Library Books (Old), Library Books-Gifts, Presidential Papers (Brewster) Pre May 2010, Presidential Papers (Brewster) Post May 2010, Oral History-Women @ Yale, Oral History-Yale, Special Collections, Departmental, A&D Gifts (June, 2012) (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
    - Book 3: Archives Services, E-Recs, GA-Departmental, Learning Plan, Public Services-Photocopy Operations, Publications, Royalties, Whitney Family Papers, Monthly Summaries-Archives, Monthly Summaries-Departmental, Miscellaneous Reports, Lindbergh Photo Project (title changed to A&D gifts), Leiwant, June 2012 (Box 3, Folder 28-30)
- Manuscript group and University records finding aid ribbon copies, Accession 2016-A-047
  - MS 1 - MS 4 (Box 1)
  - MS 5 - MS 8 (2 of 5) (Box 2)
  - MS 8 (3 of 5) - MS 18 (Box 3)
  - MS 19 - MS 25 (Box 4)
  - MS 26 - MS 33 (Box 5)
  - MS 34 - MS 45 (Box 6)
  - MS 46 - MS 56 (Box 7)
  - MS 57 - MS 63, MS 65 - MS 66, MS 68 - MS 71 (Box 8)
  - MS 72 - MS 80 (Box 9)
  - MS 81 - MS 88 (Box 10)
  - MS 89 - MS 100 (Box 11)
  - MS 101 - MS 103, MS 105 - MS 112 (Box 12)
  - MS 113 - MS 125 (Box 13)
  - MS 126 - MS 134, MS 136 (Box 14)
  - MS 137 - MS 146 (Box 15)
  - MS 147 - MS 158, MS 160 (2 of 4) (Box 16)
  - MS 160 (3 of 4) - MS 168 (Box 17)
  - MS 169 - MS 176 (Box 18)
  - MS 177 - MS 189 (Box 19)
  - MS 190 - MS 201 (Box 20)
  - MS 202 - MS 212 (2 of 8) (Box 21)
  - MS 212 (3 of 8) - MS 213 (Box 22)
  - MS 214 - MS 222 (Box 23)
  - MS 223 - MS 239 (Box 24)
  - MS 240 - MS 253, MS 255 - MS 257 (Box 25)
  - MS 258 - MS 267 (Box 26)
  - MS 268 -269, MS 271 - MS 273, MS 275 -283 (Box 27)
  - MS 284 - MS 291 (Box 28)
  - MS 292 - MS 301 (Box 29)
  - MS 303 - MS310 (Box 30)
  - MS 311 - MS 316, MS 318 - MS 322 (1 of 2) (Box 31)
  - MS 322 (2 of 2) - MS 325B (Box 32)
  - MS 326 - MS 330 (Box 33)
  - MS 331 - MS 334, MS 336 - MS 343 (4 of 5) (Box 34)
  - # 343 (5 of 5) - MS 353 (Box 35)
  - MS 354 - MS 368; National Whaling Bank Collection [no MS number assigned to it]; MS 369 - MS 372 (Box 36)
  - MS 373 - MS 378, MS 380 - MS 387 (Box 37)
  - MS 388 - MS 390, MS 392 - MS 394, MS 396 - MS 402 (Box 38)
  - MS 403 - MS 426 (Box 39)
  - MS 427 - MS 440 (Box 40)
  - MS 441 - MS 445 (3 of 4) (Box 41)
  - MS 445 (4 of 4) - MS 450 (Box 42)
  - MS 451 - MS 465 (4 of 6) (Box 43)
  - MS 465 (5 of 6) - MS 466 (15 of 25) (Box 44)
  - MS 466 (16 of 25) - MS 467 (Box 45)
  - MS 468 - MS 490 (Box 46)
  - MS 491 - MS 496A (Box 47)
  - MS 496B - MS 496E (1 of 2) (Box 48)
  - MS 496E (2 of 2) - MS 496F, MS 498 - MS 508 (Box 49)
  - MS 509 - MS 533 (Box 50)
  - MS 534 - MS 544 (Box 51)
  - MS 545 - MS 554 (Box 52)
  - MS 555 - MS 568 (Box 53)
  - MS 569 - MS 572 (Box 54)
  - MS 573 - MS 576 (5 of 8) (Box 55)
  - MS 576 (6 of 8) - MS 582 (Box 56)
  - MS 583 - MS 585, MS 587 - MS 592 (Box 57)
  - MS 593 - MS 605 (1 of 10) (Box 58)
  - MS 605 (2 of 10 ) - MS 605 (6 of 10) (Box 59)
  - MS 605 (7 of 10) - MS 609, MS 611 - MS 612, MS 614 (Box 60)
  - MS 615 - MS 627 (Box 61)
  - MS 628 (Box 62)
  - MS 629 - MS 648 (Box 63)
  - MS 649 - MS 656 (Box 64)
  - MS 657 - MS 666 (Box 65)
  - MS 667 - MS 671 (Box 66)
  - MS 672 - MS 674, MS 676 - MS 692 (Box 67)
  - MS 693 - MS 707, MS 710 - MS712 (Box 68)
  - MS 713 - MS 721, MS 723 - MS 728, MS 730 (Box 69)
  - MS 731 - MS 749 (Box 70)
  - MS 750. MS 752 - MS 757, MS 759 - MS 762 (Box 71)
  - MS 763 - MS 768 (Box 72)
  - MS 769 - MS 775 (Box 73)
  - MS 776 - MS 789 (Box 74)
  - MS 790 - MS 811 (Box 75)
  - MS 812 - MS 829 (3 of 4) (Box 76)
  - MS 829 (4 of 4) - MS 837, MS 839 - MS 849 (Box 77)
  - MS 850 - MS 862 (Box 78)
  - MS 863 - MS 879 (Box 79)
  - MS 880 - MS 884, MS 886, MS 888 - MS 895, MS 897 - MS 908 (Box 80)
  - MS 909 - MS 921, MS 923 - MS 925, MS 928 - MS 936, MS 937 - MS 942 (Box 81)
  - MS 943 - MS 959 (3 of 4) (Box 82)
  - MS 959 (4 of 4) - MS 966, MS 968 - MS 972, MS 974 - MS 987, MS 989 - MS 990 (Box 83)
  - MS 992 - MS 1000, MS 1002 - MS 1003, MS 1005 - MS 1013, MS 1015 - MS 1020, MS 1022 - MS 1024, MS 1026 - MS 1034 (Box 84)
  - MS 1035 - MS 1044 (Box 85)
  - MS 1046 - MS 1060, MS 1062 - MS 1067, MS 1069 - MS 1073, MS 1075 - 1086 (Box 86)
  - MS 1087 - MS 1099 (Box 87)
  - MS 1100 - MS 1114, MS 1116 - MS 1122, MS 1124 - MS 1137 (Box 88)
  - MS 1138 - MS 1155 (Box 89)
  - MS 1156 - MS 1160, MS 1162 - MS 1179, MS 1181 - MS 1184 (Box 90)
  - MS 1185 - MS 1196, MS 1198 - MS 1213, MS 1215 - MS 1218, MS 1220 - MS 1227 (Box 91)
  - MS 1228 - MS 1240 (Box 92)
  - MS 1241 - MS 1268 (Box 93)
  - MS 1269 - MS 1295, MS 1297 - MS 1309 (Box 94)
  - MS 1310 - MS 1321, MS 1323 - MS 1333. MS 1335 - MS 1350 (2 of 9) (Box 95)
  - MS 1350 (3 of 9) - MS 1350 (6 of 9) (Box 96)
  - MS 1350 (7 of 9) - MS 1351 (2 of 4) (Box 97)
  - MS 1350: Mexico, computer lists sorted by imprint date and author/title, 1983 November (Box 126)
  - MS 1350: Mexico, computer lists sorted by ID number, 1983 November 8 (Box 127)